

Myrto Anastasia Papapostolou

Undergraduate Informatics student



https://github.com/MyrtoP



p16papa3@ionio.gr

Skills —

Graphics, Film-Animation Editing

Photoshop, Video editing

XML,C,Python,C++

HTML5,CSS

Java



(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Hello! I'm currently an undergraduate univercity student at the department of Informatics at the Ionian University. Right now, I'm at my thtird year of my studies and I have experianced some projects, situations and lessons. At our acaademic lessons we have seen some basic knowledges like Data Base and programming with basic languages like C. I have also participated in some projects, one of them is a competition of the Udacity University and schools IEEE branch. So far, that it! If you want to learn more about me scroll down!

Education

2013 - 2016 Ph.D. High School Graduate

2016 - PresentUndergraduate Student
Majoring in Computer Science

Ionian University

Projects

Shooter Super Mario https://myrtop.github.io/Shooter/menu.html, A school project https://myrtop.github.io/Super-Mario/menu.html, A school project, which was meant to teach us the UI with the computers and the users.

Interests

Music, Drawing, Films and Movies (writing scenarios, directoring, special effects)

Experience

2017 - 2018 Participant

Udacity University

Part of a competition to build a phone app using XML.

2018/2 - 2018/4Assistant

E-evros, Alexandroupoli, Evros

Help assistant at Photoshop, taking videos, making articles etc.

2018

IEEE of Ionian University

Participated in the free project 'Local Hacathon Day', where in our

group we created the Matrix code.

Languages

English, Greek, Italian